[](https://www.codejunkies.com/default.aspx) Toggle navigation

    * [
        
        PowerSaves Prime](https://www.codejunkies.com/what-is-powersaves-prime.aspx)
        
        [
        
        PowerSaves Pro](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/PowerSaves-Pro__EF001113V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        PowerBase for Pokémon](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/PowerBase-for-Pok%C3%A9mon__EF001323V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        PowerSaves Amiibo](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/PowerSaves-for-Amiibo__EF001200.aspx)
        
        [
        
        License Key](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Powersaves-Pro-License-Key__EF001192V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        PowerPlay Upgrade](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/PowerSaves-Pro-Upgrade__EF001183.aspx)
        
    * [
        
        Go-tcha Evolve Pro+](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Go-tcha-Evolve-Pro-plus-__EF001405V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Go-tcha Expedition](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Go-tcha-Expedition__EF001396V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Go-tcha Generation](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Go-tcha-Generation__EF001354V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Go-tcha Classic Wristband](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Go-tcha-Classic__EF001336V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Go-tcha Clip](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Go-tcha-Clip__EF001338V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Limited Edition Go-tcha Ranger](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Limited-Edition-Go-tcha-Ranger__EF001302V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Go-tcha Clip Accessory Pack](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Go-tcha-Clip-Accessory-Pack__EF001346V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Go-tcha Original Accessory Pack](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Go-tcha-Accessory-Pack__EF001256.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Go-tcha Evolve](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Go-tcha-Evolve__EF001315V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Go-tcha Evolve Trainer Club Edition](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Go-tcha-Evolve-Trainer-Club-Edition__EF001335.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Go Ninja](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Go-Ninja__EF001416.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Go-tcha Tag](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Go-tcha-Tag__EF001355.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Go-tcha Ranger](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Go-tcha-Ranger__EF001297V.aspx)
        
    * [
        
        x1 Power Point](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/x1-Power-Point__EF001196.aspx)
        
        [
        
        x2 Power Points](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/x2-Power-Points__EF001208.aspx)
        
        [
        
        x5 Power Points](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/x5-Power-Points__EF001197.aspx)
        
        [
        
        x10 Power Points](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/x10-Power-Points__EF001198.aspx)
        
        [
        
        x15 Power Points](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/x15-Power-Points__EF001209.aspx)
        
        [
        
        x20 Power Points](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/x20-Power-Points__EF001210.aspx)
        
    * [
        
        NitroPro Controller - Monster Pack](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/NitroPro-Controller-Monster-Pack__EF001332.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Monster Hunter Rise](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/NitroTag-Monster-Hunter-Rise__EF001333.aspx)
        
        [
        
        NitroTag Splatoon 2](https://www.codejunkies.com/Departments/Switch/NitroTags/Splatoon-2.aspx)
        
        [
        
        NitroTag Mario Kart 8 Deluxe](https://www.codejunkies.com/Departments/Switch/NitroTags/Mario-Kart-8-Deluxe.aspx)
        
        [
        
        NitroTag Zelda Breath of the Wild](https://www.codejunkies.com/Departments/Switch/NitroTags/Zelda-Breath-of-the-Wild.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Super Mario Odyssey](https://www.codejunkies.com/Departments/Switch/NitroTags/Super-Mario-Odyssey.aspx)
        
    * [
        
        PowerSaves Amiibo](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/PowerSaves-for-Amiibo__EF001200.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Amiibo Powerbase](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/PowerBase-for-Amiibo__EF001300V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        PowerTags x10](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/x-10-Amiibo-Powertags__EF001255.aspx)
        
        [
        
        PowerTags x3](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/x-3-Amiibo-Powertags__EF001254.aspx)
        
    * [
        
        Evo Hub](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Evo-Hub__EF001241V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        CoolDog Controller for PS4](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/CoolDog-Controller-for-PS4__EF001234.aspx)
        
        [
        
        PS5 Wireless Controller](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/PS5-Wireless-Controller__EF001417.aspx)
        
    * [
        
        GameCube Action Replay](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/SD-Media-Launcher__EF000195.aspx)
        
        [
        
        SD Media Launcher](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/SD-Media-Launcher__EF000580V.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Racing Game Steering Wheel (Wii)](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/Racing-Game-Steering-Wheel-for-Wii__EF000613.aspx)
        
        [
        
        DSi/DS Action Replay Replacement USB Cable](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/DSiDS-Action-Replay-Replacement-USB-Cable__ER000015.aspx)
        
    * [
        
        CatShark](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/CatShark-Catalytic-Converter-Alarm__EF001334.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Wifi Commander Watch](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/WiFi-Commander-Watch__EF001403.aspx)
        
        [
        
        Wifi Commander Handheld](https://www.codejunkies.com/Products/WiFi-Commander__EF001404.aspx)

Product Search

Customer Service
================

* * *

Privacy Policy
--------------

#### Website Policy

This website is operated by Datel Electronics Limited , registered office, Stafford Road ,Stone, Staffordshire, ST15 0DG.

Our privacy policy sets out what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we will share it with other parties. We keep this privacy policy under review and we reserve the right to update without notice.

We are committed to keeping your personal information secure and confidential. By using our website you agree to the use of this information as set out below

#### Visitors to our website.

The website does not capture personal information other than that what you tell us when registering, buying a product, activating the product licence and in some cases when the product communicates with the site for use and uploading codes.

We use third party cookies ( see our separate cookie policy below ) such as those from Google analytics to obtain information on traffic to our site. We do not use the information in a manner which identifies the individual.

#### Children

If you are aged 13 or under please obtain your parent or guardian’s permission to providing any personal information to us. Children without this consent should not provide us with such information.

#### How we use your information.

We may use any information you give us;

* to assist us in providing products and services to you including processing credit card information via a secure third party payment gateway such as Cybersource,
* to record sales, accounting information, returns, updates and product development,
* to comply with any regulatory or legal obligation we may have from time to time.

We may also wish to use your data to inform you of any future offers and similar products. This information will not be shared with third parties. Please sign into your account and tick the option for our marketing emails If this is something you would like to sign up to , otherwise we will not send to you direct marketing emails but you can still learn about new products by visiting the website. You may unsubscribe at any time via your login.

#### What we do with your data

All the personal data we process will be processed by our staff in the UK however for the purposes of IT hosting, management and maintenance the information is located on servers within the European Union.

#### How long do we keep your data.

We retain such data for a reasonable time in the event of any legal claims and complaints however we are required by UK tax law to keep your personal data ( name, address, contact details and sales records) for a minimum of 6 years after you first provided it. If there has been no activity on your account for more than 6 years we will delete your personal data.

You have a right to request a copy of all the information we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information or have a concern about how your information is being used and or our data practices please contact us using your login details on the [support page](https://support.codejunkies.com/) of this website or if you are not already a user please create an account and request a support ticket

You may also ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate. If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law you can complain to the information commissioners office [https://ico.org.uk](https://ico.org.uk/)

* * *

#### How Can We Help?

#### Customer Service

##### Useful Links

##### Store

##### Policies

##### Service

##### Mailing List

[](javascript:void(0) "Back to Top")

Please Wait...
